wtfcalls.net 2017-10-15

# WTFcalls.com - Is there an unknown phone number on your Caller ID?

_**PRIVACY POLICY**_ _ **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**_

While you can browse sections of the site without a registered account your IP address is noted in apache logs. Any information submitted to http://wtfcalls.com becomes the property of the site and can be done with as seen fit. All notes are verified and can be removed without notice at any time for any reason. Any information submitted to the site will become public information. 

We believe that it is especially important to protect children's privacy online. We encourage parents to get involved with their children's online usage and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating. Note: We define "children" as minors younger than 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect or use any personally identifiable information from children, and we do not provide any personally identifiable information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever from our visitors younger than 13 years old. We do not knowingly allow children to participate in any of our promotions or contests. No information should be submitted to or posted at http://wtfcalls.com by visitors younger than 13 years old. In the event that http://wtfcalls.com obtains information from an individual who indicates that he/she is younger than 13 years old, http://wtfcalls.com will promptly discard the personally identifiable information without collecting, using or disclosing such information to any third party. You should be aware that if your child voluntarily discloses his or her name, e-mail address or other information on any Web site, such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages.

_**Links to Other Sites**_

This site contains links to other sites. While we encourage our business partners to adopt privacy policies that build users' trust and confidence in the Internet, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web sites linked to any of our sites. We may allow third parties to sponsor promotions and sweepstakes through our site. Use of any personal information provided to such a third party will be governed by that party's privacy policy.

_**Contact Us**_

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to support
